fcxnewsonline.com 2017-07-08

# Privacy Policy

Punk Share ("Punk Share," "we" or "us") is committed to being a safe place for our users to anonymously share their innermost thoughts, secrets, and feelings. That’s why we place so much focus on protecting your privacy and personal information.

This Privacy Policy covers the Punk Share website ("Site") and any Punk Share application or service ("Services"). It explains how our Site or Services collect, use, protect, and disclose personal information, Usage data, and Message data (we define these last two terms below). Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of, or content on, third party services or other properties to which our Site or the Services link, or into which our Services are embedded or incorporated (e.g., Punk Share embeds).

### What Information We Collect

#### Personal Information and Anonymity

We collect very little information that could be used to identify you personally. A non-unique username is randomly assigned to you that you may change at any time. If you change your username, please be sure to create a username that doesn’t disclose any personally identifying information. If you decide to invite your friends to use the Services via our “invite friends” feature, you will also need to reveal your cell phone number to your friend when you send the invitation. No mobile number or email address is ever stored on our servers.

Our goal is to provide you with a tool that allows you to express yourself while remaining anonymous to the community. However, please keep in mind that your pranks will be publicly viewable, so if you want to preserve your anonymity you should not include any personal information in your pranks. In addition, when you allow us to collect latitude and longitude location information from your device by enabling locations services, your general location (e.g., town) and proximity to other users when you post, will also be publicly viewable. Therefore, even if you do not include personal information in your pranks, your use of the Services may still allow others, over time, to make a determination as to your identity based on the content of your pranks as well as your general location. For instance, if you work in a small organization and post pranks about your working experience, it is possible that at some point a co-worker will be able to identify you. This is part of the nature of the Services, and we encourage you to be careful and avoid including details that may be used by others to identify you.

#### Usage Data

We automatically collect usage information. This doesn’t tell us who a user is, though. It just lets us collect information about how people access and use our Services. This collected information is called Usage Data. We gather it so we can get a better portrait of how our users are interacting with the Site and Services so that we can continue to improve the user experience over time.

Here are a few examples of Usage Data:

When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information about the type of device you’re using, the operating system version on your device and your IP Address. Or if you’re using the Site, we automatically collect information about your operating system, web browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), and your network-enabled machine’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, as well as the pages you view, and the time and length of your visit. This data helps us analyze trends and user behaviors, manage the site, and enhance or update our Services. In other words, it helps us give you a better experience by understanding and reacting to the ways that users interact with the Services and Site.

While you’re downloading or using our mobile applications or Services, we may ask for, access, or track location-based information such as device-provided latitude or longitude, if you have location services enabled for the application. One reason for doing this is to help you explore postings in your area or for us to determine how many postings come from a particular area. If you are using an Android device, our Services may continue to run in the background. In this instance, your device may also periodically send us location information. However, giving us permission to access or track any location-based data is absolutely voluntary. In fact, you may freely opt into or opt out of location-based portions of our Services at any time using the app- or device-level settings on iOS or the device-level settings on Android. However, please bear in mind that, even if you have disabled location services, we may still determine your city, state, and country location based on your IP address (but not your exact location).

#### Cookies

Like many other websites, our Site uses cookies. These are small, removable data files that your web browser stores to help identify your computer and browser when you visit a website. They can also have the added benefit of speeding up your access to sites. We don’t use cookies to collect personal information. Instead, we use them to improve the quality of our Site and Services. Our Site is not designed to respond to “do not track” signals received from browsers.

Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to let you know when a cookie is being sent.

Some of the Service Providers (we define this below) that we work with may use their own cookies in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. We don’t have access or control over these cookies. The use of cookies by these third parties isn’t covered by our Privacy Policy. You should review the applicable third party privacy policy for sites who link to our embed our content.

### How We May Use Your Information

We use the information that we collect from you for internal purposes. This includes offering you access to the Site and Services, letting you know when we have new products or Services, and communicating with you in other ways.

We will not share your information except in the cases explained below.

### How We May Disclose Your Information

Punk Share is committed to the privacy and security of your information, including preserving your anonymity; however, there are a few cases when we will be unable to do so. Here are a few situations where we may disclose the information that we collect from you.

#### First, we respect the Law

This means that we may disclose information such as your created pranks, Chat Data, IP address, and your location, if known, if we have a good faith belief it is necessary to comply with applicable laws, regulations, legal processes (such as a subpoena or court order) or enforceable governmental requests. If you want to learn more about how we do that, please review our Law Enforcement Response Guide.

#### Second, we expect you to respect the Law as well

Punk Share is not a place to harbor criminals. You must not use the Site or Services to plan, incite, promote, or showcase any criminal act is strictly prohibited. This includes statements revealing plans or actions around human trafficking, sexual exploitation, or predation. These types of behaviors are against our mission, constitute a breach of our Terms of Service, and more importantly, are illegal. If you engage in any illegal activity we may be required, or choose to, share the information we may have about you with the appropriate authorities.

#### Third, we don't want anybody to be harmed

Punk Share is meant to be a safe place. There may be situations where we may need to disclose the information we may have about you for the greater good, such as if we see suicidal statements or statements that involve the intent to harm oneself or others, or learn information about missing children, or threats to the community.

#### We may also share your information for technical reasons

From time to time, we may establish business relationships with other businesses but will only do so if we believe they are trustworthy. We carefully vet these relationships to confirm that these service providers have privacy practices that are consistent with ours. These service providers may include companies that provide us with services such as hosting and maintenance, customer relationship management, push notifications, and data storage and management.

We give service providers only the information that’s necessary for them to perform services on our behalf. What’s more, each service provider must agree to use security procedures and practices that are reasonable and appropriate for the information involved. This is another way that we work to protect your information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Also, we prohibit our service providers from using your information in any manner that is not specified by us.

In addition, we may use and disclose certain Usage Data to third parties. This Usage Data doesn’t identify individual users. We use mobile analytics software to help us better understand how our Services work on your device. This software may only record information usage information, such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded. But we do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile app. This essentially only covers what you do, but not who does it. We may also partner with universities or other research institutions or scientists to use the limited information we have in anonymous, controlled research studies.

#### Affiliates and Corporate Transactions

We may share the information that we collect from you with businesses that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with Punk Share. This also means that if Punk Share is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer such information in connection with that particular transaction.

#### Information Security

Punk Share is committed to protecting the security of your personal information and Message Data. This is why we employ security measures designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized access (for instance we encrypt private messages). Regardless of our efforts, however, no data transmission over the Internet or other network, including any of Punk Share’s services, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We will do our part, but we can’t and don’t guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services. Thus, any information you transmit is sent at your own risk.

#### Protecting Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 17. You must be over the age of 17 to use our Site and Services. If we determine you are under 17 we may in our discretion decide to ban you from the Services.

#### Your Information may be maintained outside of your jurisdiction

Please be advised that we process and store all information in the United States or other countries where our service providers may be based. This may be important to you, as the laws of the United States or such other countries may not be as protective of your personal information as the laws of your jurisdiction.

#### Deleting your account

Upon your request, we delete your account. You may make such request by emailing [contact@punkshare.com](mailto:contact@punkshare.com).

#### Opting Out of Push Notifications

You are free to opt out of push notifications from our Services at any time. To turn off notifications, be sure that you have those settings turned off both in the Punk Share settings and in the settings on your mobile device.

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may periodically change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll inform you here or by posting a prominent notice on the homepage of our Site. Any changes become effective when we post them on the Site. The date of any new posting is indicated by the “Last Updated” date in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Site, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail them to [contact@punkshare.com](mailto:contact@punkshare.com). Please do not email us any sensitive information.
